{
    "questions": [
        {
            "qid": 1,
            "question": " Which of the following widgets use for layout?",
            "options": [
                "Text",
                "Column",
                "Expanded",
                "Inkwell"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        
        {
            "qid": 2,
            "question": "Flutter supports cross platform development",
            "options": [
                "False",
                "True"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "qid": 3,
            "question": "Which of these components is not a built-in widget of Flutter?",
            "options": [
                "FloatingButton",
                "AppBar",
                "TextTransformer",
                "TextStyle"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        },
        
        {
            "qid": 4,
            "question": "Which of the following properties must we utilize for adding the label, inline, and icon suggestion text to the TextField widget?",
            "options": [
                "InputDecoration",
                "ListView",
                "SizedBox",
                "shrinkWrap:true"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "qid": 5,
            "question": "How to fix following error in Flutter?\nA RenderFlex overflowed by...",
            "options": [
                "By removing relevent error-causing widget",
                "By wrapping up the relevent error-causing widget with expanded widget",
                "By running the command 'flutter clean'",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "qid": 6,
            "question": "What is the correct widget for using image as a icon in flutter?",
            "options": [
                "Image(\n  type: icon,\n  child:(...)\n)",
                "ImageIcon(...)",
                "IconImage(...)",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "qid": 7,
            "question": "Can we change the state with any widget in stateless widget?",
            "options": [
                "No",
                "Yes"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "qid": 8,
            "question": "Which of the following is not a type of http request?",
            "options": [
                "put",
                "delete",
                "update",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "qid": 9,
            "question": "Which of the following is not a type of widget lifecycle method?",
            "options": [
                "didUpdateState()",
                "didUpdateWidget()",
                "didChangeDependencies()",
                "deactivate()"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "qid": 10,
            "question": "What do you understand about BuildContext in flutter?",
            "options": [
                "Each BuildContext is unique to a widget.",
                "BuildContext is a locator that is used to track each widget in a tree and locate them and their position in the tree.",
                "The BuildContext of each widget is passed to their build method.",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 4
        }
    ]
}